
--- SAL-QTN-2024-00478 (1) (1).pdf ---
Error reading SAL-QTN-2024-00478 (1) (1).pdf 'charmap' codec can't encode character '\ufb00' in position 19: character maps to <undefined>

--- SAL-QTN-2026-00004.pdf ---
Error reading SAL-QTN-2026-00004.pdf 'charmap' codec can't encode character '\ufb00' in position 19: character maps to <undefined>

--- SAL-QTN-2026-00476.pdf ---
Error reading SAL-QTN-2026-00476.pdf 'charmap' codec can't encode character '\ufb00' in position 19: character maps to <undefined>

--- Alamo Components.pdf ---
Call Point / Transmitter with Bedside Button
Patient call point with Call, Cancel, Acknowledge and Housekeeping
buttons. This module also has 2 RJ11 ports to connect accessories and a
power port to connect an adapter if needed.
Patient side call switch accessories that can be connected to the main call
point. The switch is connected to the call point via coil cord and can be
placed near bed. It makes it easier for patients to make nurse calls.
Room Light
Indicator lights to be placed outside the room doors. These lights can be paired with call
points so that they light up when a call is made.
Alamo Nurse Call Components
Central Reciever / Gateway
Gateway receives messages from
the call points and shares the data
with other devices. It can be a
mobile phone, tablets, android tv or
cloud server
Nursing Station Monitor
Software
Device with call system
software installed, it can be a
tablet, mobile phone or
computer.
Alamo Manager
Call Points administration software to install manage and reconfigure call points
and lights. It also helps see the status of each button and generate preventive
maintenance reports.
Alamo Vision
Nurse call reports and escalations application for nursing Managers. Get reports
on peak timings, and alerts if calls are not attended within the stipulated time,
View the data nursing station-wise.
Bed Unit
Bathroom Unit
Room Indicator
Nursing Station
Call Point / Transmitter with Pull Cord
This module also has 2 RJ11 ports to connect accessories and a power port to
connect an adapter if needed. As the transmitter is separate it reduces the
risk of getting pulled off by users.Pull Cord accessory that can be connected
to a call point for use in washrooms for ease of access.
Nursing Managers / CNO
Maintenance Managers

--- SAL-QTN-2024-00478 (1) (1).pdf ---
Error reading SAL-QTN-2024-00478 (1) (1).pdf 'charmap' codec can't encode character '\ufb00' in position 19: character maps to <undefined>

--- SAL-QTN-2026-00004.pdf ---
Error reading SAL-QTN-2026-00004.pdf 'charmap' codec can't encode character '\ufb00' in position 19: character maps to <undefined>

--- SAL-QTN-2026-00476.pdf ---
Error reading SAL-QTN-2026-00476.pdf 'charmap' codec can't encode character '\ufb00' in position 19: character maps to <undefined>
